（忆往昔）
你真的能打败她吗
Can you really beat her?
我可以
I can.
那么好
Then, yes.
迪恩 他不是小卡
Dean, that's not Cass!
被发现了
Cat's out.
- 路西法 - 路西法
- Lucifer. - Lucifer.
太久以来 掌舵之人懦弱低能
We have had a coward and a fool at the helm for too long.
我还是你的主人
I'm still your master.
我是不是把你从狗舍里放出来太早了
Did I let you out of that kettle too soon?
你的小脑瓜里
What treasonous thoughts do you have.
琢磨什么叛逆的念头呢
brewing in that little head of yours?
如果你觉得你能打败阿玛拉
If you thought you could beat Amara,
你就会主动去找她
you'd be taking the fight to her.
你不够强大
You're not strong enough.
我现在或许有些准备不足
I may be a bit under-equipped.
你知道纳粹有个专门进行
Did you know the Nazis had a special branch.
考古的分支吗
devoted to archaeology?
那是什么 我的爱人
What is that, mon amour?
里面提到了一件超能武器
And they speak of a super weapon.
是吗 是什么
Yeah? What was it?
「上帝之手」
"The Hand of God."
但同作为记录者我跟你说一句
From Man of Letters to Man of Letters?
我正在未来打一场仗
I'm fighting a war in the future.
跟你的战争不同
It's not like your war.
这场战争很大 像圣经 我需要你的武器获胜
It's big, Biblical, and I need your weapon to win.
和阿玛拉有联系的是迪恩
Dean's the one with the link to Amara,
我为什么要放过你
why have I been trying to spare you?
没能量了
It's kicked.
谁能想到上帝之手
Who'd have thought the hand of God.
只能打一炮
would turn out to be a one-hitter?
（如今）
这场比赛非常激烈 各位
This is a barn burner, folks.
精彩纷呈
Off the ropes.
把他抱了起来
Picks him up and…
背部击碎
Oh, it's a back breaker.
（密苏里州 布里姆森）
但只数了两个数
Oh, but only a two count.
新手肖恩·哈利没能击败「绞刑人」
The rookie, Shawn Harley, fails to take "The hangman" down.
脖子遭到重击
A stinger to the neck.
你现在还醉着吗
Are you seriously drunk right now?
闭嘴 做好准备
Just shut up and get ready.
背部又遭一击
Ooh, and it's a stinger to the back.
他要不行了
He's going in.
他被打到场边
Takes him to the turnbuckle.
好诶
Yeah!
我们知道接下来会怎样
Oh, and we know what's coming next.
来吧
Bring it on, baby!
都结束了
It's all over.
我要吊死他
I'm gonna hang his ass.
好啊
Oh, yeah, baby.
结束了 各位
It's all over now, folks.
输家被吊起来了
We have lift-off.
哈利呼吸困难了
As Harley struggling to breathe now.
他脸色发青了
He's turning blue.
好啊
Yeah!
有人看见我的绳子了吗
Hey, has anyone seen my rope?
搞什么 我刚刚差点没命
What the hell? I almost died out there.
哈利 别闹
Harley, back off.
你要站在这酒鬼这边吗 不是吧
You're gonna take the wino's side? Really?
不是这样的
That's not what this is…
不管了
Whatever.
你们这些老家伙总是抱团 是吧
You old-timers like to stick together, right?
帮个忙
Well, do us a favor…
看好你的人
Keep a leash on your boy.
否则他可能要受伤
or he might get hurt.
[邪恶力量 第11季第15集]
你有没有看见
Have you seen the, um…
嗯 谢了
Yeah. Thanks.
干杯
Yeah, bottoms up.
嗯
Yeah.
包怎么回事
What's with the bag?
还记得最强摔跤吗
You remember Top Notch wrestling?
嗯
Yeah.
小时候爸爸带我们
Those, uh, wrestling shows.
去看过的摔跤比赛
dad took us to when we were kids.
是的
Right.
昨晚看到一则讣告
Came across an obituary last night.
「绞刑人」拉瑞·李死了
Larry "The hangman" Lee died.
不
Oh, no.
- 他不是… - 爸爸最喜欢的了
- Wasn't he, uh… - He was dad's favorite.
每次绞索悬下来
Every time that noose would come out,
爸爸都会站起来
dad would be up on his feet.
我很少能看到他
Yeah, that was one of the few times.
那么开心的样子
I ever saw him actually happy.
是啊 我记得
Yeah. I remember that.
总之 葬礼距这里不到一天的路
Anyway, the, uh, funeral's less than a day's drive.
我们去悼念一下吧
I say we go pay our respects.
你不觉得我们现在有点忙吗
Don't you think o-our plates are a little full?
外面情况很糟啊 迪恩
I mean, it's bad out there, Dean.
是啊 萨姆 你以为我不知道吗
Yeah, Sam. You think I don't know that?
我们这一周完全沉浸在查传说里
We've done nothing but mainline lore for a week, okay?
我们没查到任何其他上帝之手或是阿玛拉的资料
We've got jack on another hand of God and Amara,
救小卡的办法更是没找到
and we've got even less jack on how to save Cass.
如果他想被我们救的话
If he wants to be saved.
他当然想
He does…
就算他自己还不知道
Even if he doesn't know it yet.
- 迪恩 - 我累坏了
- Dean… - I'm burnt, man. Okay?
我…我们需要离开这里
And I need… we need to get out of here.
去伸伸腿吧
Let's go stretch our legs.
好
Oh, good.
很好
Yes.
记住 ABC
Remember, a-b-c…
「一定要成功」
"Always be closing."
你们越早给我找到另一个上帝之手
The sooner you little storm clouds find me another hand of god,
我就越开心
the happier I will be.
你希望我开心的 是吧 美女
You want me to be happy, don't you, dollface?
当然 陛下
Of course, my lord.
答得好
Good answer.
好了
All right.
上天入地 东奔西跑 到处找
You're gonna look high, look low, far and wide.
搜遍每个仓库 每户农舍
Search every warehouse, every farmhouse,
母鸡舍 屋外厕所 狗舍
every henhouse, outhouse, and doghouse.
你呢 小狗狗
What about you, little puppy?
你有什么要补充的吗
You have something to add?
没有 主人
Nothing, master.
真的吗
Really?
否则我肯定会说的
I would tell you. I swear.
我相信你
I believe you.
我可以继续干活儿了吗
May I return to my task?
当然
Of course.
但要改一下
Just one minor tweak.
用你的舌头
Use your tongue.
哥们 看啊
Dude, check it out.
是「尖叫」卡西·莱昂斯
It's "The scream" Casey Lyons.
是啊
Oh, yeah.
「破碎球」卡尔霍恩
There's wrecking ball Calhoon.
布鲁克林野兽
The Brooklyn beast?
他们都怎么了
What happened to 'em?
他们都…残了
They're all…broken.
哥们 哥们
Dude. Dude.
那是加纳·劳里斯啊
Gunnar freakin' Lawless.
你也太迷弟了吧
Groupie much?
闭嘴
Shut up.
我该去打招呼吗 我该去打招呼
Should I go say hi? I should go say hi.
我去打招呼了
I'm gonna go say hi.
我知道这很难过 保重
I know it's hard. All right, take care.
先生
Hi, s-sir.
我看到你站在这边
I, uh, saw you… saw you standing over here.
就跟我弟弟说我该过来打个招呼
and told my brother that I-I should come over and say hi,
所以我就过来了
So I came over and, uh…
你好
Hi.
加纳·劳里斯
Gunnar Lawless.
我知道
Oh, I know.
哥们 我跟你说
Man, I-I got to tell you.
我…
I…
小时候非常崇拜你
worshiped you, growing up.
多谢 这手我还要呢
Thanks. I plan on keeping that hand.
抱歉
Oh, sorry.
我…10岁的时候
You know, when I was… when I was 10,
第一次擅闯民宅
I got my first b&e.
就是因为想借别人家的付费电视
from borrowing some family's pay-per-view.
看你和力量之塔的
so that I could watch the cage match.
铁笼擂台赛
between you and the Tower Of Power.
我不知道该对
I'm not sure how I feel about.
害你年少时犯罪作何感想
contributing to your juvenile delinquency,
但还是多谢了
but appreciate it all the same.
嗯 对了 当年该你获胜的
Yeah, uh… You were robbed, by the way.
当然了
You bet your ass I was.
好棒
Oh, yes.
你是莉奥
You're Rio.
你以前是「超级炸弹」桑切斯的经纪人 是吧
Y-you used to manage superbomb Sanchez, right?
那是很久之前了
That was a long time ago.
是啊 但是你
Well, yeah, b-but you… you…
你可真美
you look great.
抱歉
Sorry. Uh…
场合不合适
wrong place.
只是你是我…第一个暗恋对象
It's just y-you were my… my first crush.
你不是那种
You weren't one of those guys.
把我的海报挂在床头的男人吧
that had my poster above his bed, were you?
什么 没有
What? No.
你还做经纪人吗
Are you still managing?
我偶尔会主持比赛
I call some matches sometimes,
但大部分时候都在幕后
but I'm mostly behind the curtain, you know,
预订比赛 照顾拳手
booking the shows and taking care of the guys.
嗯 有人去世一定很难过
Yeah. Must be hard to see one go.
是啊
Yeah, well…
我们一起做巡回很久了
We spent a lot of time on the road together.
就像一家人
We're like family,
最近 我有太多的家人入土了
and lately, I've seen too many of my boys be put in the dirt.
我跟绞刑人认识25年了
I knew hangman for 25 years.
他是个好人
He was a good man.
家庭美满
Great family.
我真不敢相信他会这么对我们
I just can't believe he would do this.
什么
Do what?
自杀
Kill himself.
等等 讣告里没写啊
Wait. That wasn't in the obituary.
他的家人不想广而告之
Ah, the family didn't want that advertised,
所以
so…
说起来 我失陪了
Speaking of which, if you'll excuse me.
可怜人
Poor son of a bitch.
是啊
Yeah.
据说
You know, uh, word is…
嗯 我听说了
Yeah. I heard.
知道吗 他们今晚打算举办纪念赛
Hey, you know they're having a memorial show tonight?
我知道你急着回去 但是
And I know you're itching to get back, but, uh…
我们该去
We should go to it.
真的
Really?
何不呢
Why not?
反正明天世界还是那么一团糟
World's still gonna be screwed tomorrow, right?
- 布鲁克林野兽回归对阵拉什 - 嗯
- The Brooklyn beast returns against Rush - Yeah.
- 展开史诗般的铁人大战 - 好嘞
- in an epic iron man matchup! - All right.
喊起来吧
Let me hear you make some noise.
准备好了吗
Are you ready?
我印象中最强赛要更…
You know, I remember the Top Notch shows being…
盛大 是最强的嘛
grander, you know? Top-notch.
是啊 如果你多喝点
Yeah. Well, you drink enough,
会有种回到过去的感觉的
it'll be just like old times.
莉奥
Rio.
- 你个混蛋 - 得了
- You dog. - Oh, shut up.
哥们 我们在守灵上认识的 她很和气
Dude, we met at the wake. She's nice.
你小时候不是还在床头
Did you tell you used to have a poster of her.
挂过她的海报吗
over your bed when you were a kid?
才没有
No.
- 得了 - 听着
- Yeah. - Get this.
守灵时有个人告诉我他们今晚才能挣25美元
Guy at the wake told me they're only making 25 bucks tonight.
- 就这么点 - 嗯
- That's it? - Yeah.
这哪值得
Now, that hardly seems worth it.
想想看
Yeah, think about that.
一个个小镇地打 为了一点零花
Town after town, putting your ass on the line.
冒生命危险
for next to nothing?
没有钱 没有荣誉
No money. No glory.
你知道你刚刚描述了我们的工作吧
You realize you just literally described our jobs.
抱歉 两位
Excuse me, fellas.
- 没事 - 没事
- It's all right. - It's all right.
- 这肯定精彩 - 是啊
- This is gonna be great. - Yeah.
这样的精彩谁会不喜欢 是吧
Got to love some rasslin', am I right?
嗯
Yeah.
啤酒便宜 孩子也高兴
Beer's cheap, kid's entertained…
这就是做爹啊
parenting.
记住 别跟妈妈说哦
Remember, don't tell mom how many I've had.
嗯 这让我回到过去了
Yeah. Now, that brings me back.
你能不能别毁掉老爸为我们做的
You want to not try and ruin one of the nicest things.
- 最棒的一件事 - 女士们先生们
- dad ever did for us, please? - Ladies and gentlemen…
- 多谢 - 好诶
- Thank you. - Yeah!
- 请为地狱剃刀鼓掌 - 好诶
- …Put your hands together for hellrazor! - Yeah.
要上场了
Almost showtime.
我有东西给你
Got a little something for ya.
现在 女士们先生们
And now, ladies and gentlemen,
请为加纳·劳里斯鼓掌
Put your hands together for Gunnar Lawless!
好诶
Yeah!
Oh, yeah!
好诶
是吧 是吧
Right?! Right?!
起来 放尊重点
Hey, get up. Show some respect.
谁要 谁要
Who's getting it? Who's getting it, huh?
记得吗 他摘下手套
Remember this? This is where he takes a glove off.
然后在赛前送给个孩子
and gives it to some kid before the match?
好诶
Oh, yeah! Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
好棒
Cool.
好吧
Okay.
下次吧
Maybe next time.
没事 我又不是小孩子
It's all right. I'm not a child.
没事的
It's fine.
一脚对脸
Big foot to the face!
劳里斯踩上绳子
Lawless up on the ropes now.
起来
Get up!
起来啊 伙计
Get up, buddy.
加油 伙计
Come on, man.
你行的 加纳
You can do it, Gunnar.
起来啊 伙计
Get up, buddy.
来啊 哥们
Come on, man.
摆脱他
Get out of it!
加纳
Gunnar!
了结他 了结他
Up and over! Up and over!
1 2 3
1, 2, 3!
我去撒个尿 乖乖的
I got to drain the dragon. Be good.
结束喽 各位
But it's all over now, folks.
太棒了
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
好了 可以走了
All right, you guys are good.
伙计 别太难过了 好吗
Hey, buddy, try to keep your head up, okay?
走吧
Come on. Let's go.
可怜的孩子
Poor kid.
- 是啊 - 怎么说的
- Yeah. - What'd they say?
你不会相信的
You're not gonna believe this.
尸体 被刻了标记
The body…was marked.
什么东西弄的
By what?
他跟剪刀手爱德华玩挠痒痒来着吗
What, he get in a tickle fight with Edward Scissorhands?
拜托
Dude.
听我说 伤痕看上去是故意弄的
Look. T-the cuts look deliberate, you know?
- 像仪式 - 怎么 你觉得是有案子吗
- Ritualistic. - What, you think this is a case?
你觉得没有吗
You think it's not?
好吧 你有什么想法
Okay. What are you thinking?
我不知道 女巫吗
I don't know. A-a witch, maybe?
这样吧 我回旅馆查查这个符号
You know what? I'll head back to the motel, look into the symbol.
我留下 到处问问
I'll stay here, shake some trees.
有人吗
Hello?
联调局 有些问题要问
FBI. I got some questions.
布勒
Bueller?
好诶
Oh, yeah!
漂亮
Nice moves.
天呐 你没事吧
Oh, my God. A-are you all right?
嗯 很好
Yeah, good.
联调局 鲁西莫夫探员
Agent, uh, Roussimoff, FBI.
你也去了守灵 不是吗
Y-you were at the wake, weren't you?
是的
I was.
嗯 然后死了人 就又得开始上班了
Yeah, and then the body dropped, and back on the clock.
你认识死者吗
Did you know the deceased?
我给他卖过票
Oh, I-I sold him some tickets.
他有个孩子 是吧
He had a kid, right?
是啊
Yeah.
或许我的人是对的
Maybe my boys are right.
或许我们真的被诅咒了
Maybe we really are cursed.
诅咒
Cursed?
在我们巡回第一站 什里夫波特
Back in Shreveport, our first stop on the tour,
一个维护人员在海外退伍军人协会后的垃圾箱里
a maintenance guy foy d a body stashed in a dumpster.
发现了一具尸体
behind the VFW,
现在又是这种事
and now this.
能给我一张你们人员的完整名单吗
Could I get a list of your whole crew?
摔跤手 助理 所有随行人员
Wrestlers, roadies, anybody that you roll with.
布置租赁赛场都是用当地人
We use locals for all the setups and concessions.
我只能带着拳手上路
I can only afford to travel my boys.
他们现在在哪
And where would they be right now?
最近的酒吧吧
Try the nearest bar.
反正我是要去那儿
I know that's where I'll be.
好 谢谢
Okay. Thanks.
天呐
God.
我们没多少时间
We don't have much time.
我要救你出去
I'm getting you out of here.
现在
Now.
我不能走
I can't leave.
你可以 你还有朋友的
You can. You still have friends…
有些人希望你回来 希望路西法滚蛋
People who want you back… who want Lucifer gone.
我不知道他把你怎么了
I don't know what he's done to you.
我无法想象 但你…
I can't imagine, but you're…
你不是奴隶 或是狗
You're not a slave, a dog.
你是克劳力
You're Crowley,
魔鬼应该怕你才对
and the devil should be afraid of you.
迪恩 是吧
Dean, right?
嗯
Yeah.
比赛看得开心吗
You enjoy the show?
简直太棒了
The show was great.
嗯 你很棒
Yeah, yeah. You were great.
比赛之后的事就不太好了
After the show, not so much, but, uh…
是啊 我听说了
Yeah, I heard.
真是遗憾
It's a damn shame.
嗯
Yeah.
我就是为此而来
That's, uh, kind of why I'm here.
怎么不早说啊
Kind of buried the lead on that one, huh?
- 谢谢 - 不客气
- Thanks. - You're welcome.
但听说最强比赛出这种事不是第一次了
But I hear this isn't the first murder at a Top Notch show.
场上场下 都是群不好惹的人
It's a rough crowd… inside the ring and out.
是啊
Yeah.
92年
'92.
我离开赛场后 几个无赖
I'm leaving the ring and some damn reprobate.
拿着破碎的酒瓶来打我
goes at me with a broken beer bottle.
几年前
A couple years ago,
有个犯人袭击了我
a, uh, perp got the drop on me,
决定带走一小块腿留念
decided to take a chunk of my leg as a keepsake.
看见这个了吗
See this right here?
这几根手指能屈能伸
Far as I can bend these.
还多亏了四百磅的约拿·兰西德
thanks to good ol' Jonah Rancid and all 400 pounds of him.
一下压在了我身上
just dropping down on me.
好嘞
Sure thing.
但你还在比赛
But yet you're still out there, still doing it.
我挨过打 被人吐过口水
I've been beat up, spit on,
被捅伤过 挨过揍
stabbed, roughed up,
但我绝对总要再站起来
but I will be damned if I didn't always get back up.
我明白的一个道理
One thing I learned…
就是不管遭遇什么 你都得继续撑着
you got to keep on grinding no matter what's thrown your way.
你真棒
Damn, you're awesome.
跟我几个前妻说去啊
Tell that to my ex-wives.
失陪一下
Give me a sec.
- 查到什么了 - 不少
- Hey, what do you got? - A lot, actually.
最强巡回每一站
So every stop on the Top Notch tour,
都会死人
somebody turned up dead.
并不都是在场馆发生
It didn't all happen at the venue,
而且大部分看上去像意外
and most of them look like accidents,
但他们都有那个符号 包括绞刑人
but they all had the symbol… hangman, too.
他不是自杀的吗
Well, I thought he killed himself.
是啊 莉奥是那么说
Yeah, that's what Rio said,
但警方没有结案
but the cops are treating it like an open case.
他们认为 原话是
They're thinking, and I quote,
「是奇怪的撒旦崇拜的玩意」
"It's some kind of weird satanic crap."
这可好
Awesome.
是啊 还有更好的
Yeah, it gets better.
那个符号 是古苏美尔文
That symbol… ancient Sumerian.
据说有「汲取生命之火」的力量
Said to have the power to "Pluck the spark of life."
什么意思
And that means?
灵魂吗
Souls, maybe?
那么是恶魔喽
So we're talking demon?
值得一查
It's worth checking out.
莉奥说他们雇本地人布置场馆
Well, Rio says that they use locals to set up, so…
那么就是其中一个摔跤手了
So it's got to be one of the wrestlers.
或许吧
Maybe.
好吧 赶紧过来
All right. Just get here.
你打算怎么办
What are you gonna do?
我还在想
I'm working on it.
喂
Yo!
亲爱的
Sweetheart!
再来一杯
Hit me again!
哈利
Hey, Harley.
悠着点 你已经喝不少了
Go easy. I think you've had enough.
去死
Screw off.
只是想帮忙
Just trying to help.
就像在沃斯堡市那样吗
Like you helped me in Fort Worth?
怎么
What?
你以为我不知道是你不让我上场吗
You think I don't know you got me kicked off the card?
你不肯去快餐店帮忙 这我没法忍
You wouldn't job to Crazy D., and I couldn't abide by that.
是啊
Yeah.
我觉得你是受不了
I think you just can't stand the thought.
被我抢风头
of me stealing your thunder.
小子 这我完全不担心
Kid, I got no worries about that.
行了
All right.
够了
That's enough.
起来啊 老家伙
Get up, old man.
还是你得嗑点特效药
Or do you need your go-juice?
什么
What?
没错
That's right.
我看到他和他的毒贩了
I saw him and his dealer.
你的金童是个嗑药的
Your golden boy's a freaking junkie.
他在说谎
He's lying.
- 去你妈的 - 好了 好了
- Like hell. - All right, all right.
哈利 还有两天才到孟菲斯市
Harley, we got two days till memphis.
去把酒劲睡醒
Sleep it off.
加纳 这事咱明天再说
Gunnar, I'll talk to you about this tomorrow.
走
Go.
你没事吧
You okay?
没事 没事
Ah, yeah, yeah.
我被下手更狠 身体更壮的汉子打过
I've been hit harder by guys a lot tougher.
嗯
Yeah.
你为什么不还手
Why, uh … why didn't you fight back?
我不需要证明什么
I got nothing to prove.
- 你没事吧 老大 - 没事
- You okay, boss? - Yeah.
又是寻常的一天 是吧
Just another day, huh?
来 敬你…
Well, hey. Here's, uh …
能大人大量
Here's to being the bigger man, right?
谢了
Obliged.
咱还得多喝几杯
We're gonna need more shots.
很多杯
A lot more.
这边
This way.
我没有…
Uh I wasn't …
她逼我的
She made me.
你怎么…
How did you …
我是克劳力
I'm Crowley.
迪恩
Dean?
Dean.
哥们 你没事吧
Dude, you okay?
没事
Yeah.
怎么回事
What happened?
主要是龙舌兰
Mostly tequila…
掺了点圣水
Cut with holy water.
我请所有摔跤手都喝了酒
I bought drinks for all the wrestlers,
然后 他们就说
And then, you know, they're like,
「你也得喝啊」
"Well, you got to drink, too."
天 他们太能喝了 尤其是莉奥
Oh, man, they can drink, especially Rio.
我仿佛都听到我的肝在咆哮了
I think I heard my liver screaming at me.
那么 有人有反应吗
So, did anyone react?
没有
No.
你让他们每个人都喝了
And you got them all?
除了哈利
Uh, except, uh, Harley,
那个终极混蛋
the ultimate douchebag.
我还没靠近他就先走了
He bailed before I could get to him.
这里怎么这么亮啊
Why is it so bright in here?
好吧 咱们去找他
All right. Let's go find him.
好
Okay.
伙计
Dude!
来了
I'm coming.
哈利
Harley.
这可不妙
Well, that's not good.
还用你说
Uh, ya think?
陛下
My lord?
这顺耳多了
That's better.
现在去找我藏的王牌吧
Now let's go find the ace up my sleeve.
看这个 过来
Hey, check this out. Come here.
- 有发现了 - 对 监控录像
- Got something? - Yeah, uh, security-cam footage.
好吧 看看有没有收获
All right, let's see if we got anything.
这是半夜1：07 哈利往他房间去了
Um, so this is 1:07 A.M. Harley heads to his room.
- 这是… - 不知道
- Who's… - No idea.
但进去了几分钟 那是哈利
But, in there for a few minutes, and that's harley.
看来他被弄晕了
He looks knocked out.
对
Yeah.
再看看
Now, let's see.
劳里斯
Lawless?
如果哈利是恶魔 加纳是怎么放倒他的
If Harley is a demon, then how did Gunnar get the drop on him?
咱们去找他问问就知道了
Let's find him and ask him.
救命
Help!
哥们 什么情况
Dude, what the hell is going on?
听着
Look.
我知道我之前很混蛋
I know I've been a dick,
很抱歉 行吗
but I'm sorry, okay?
我之前攻击了你
I took a shot at you.
那很过分 很…
It was a cheap shot. It was …
很下作
it was a cheap-ass shot.
我只是…
And I just…
求你别伤害我
just don't hurt me.
求你了
Please.
这由不得我决定
It's not my call.
你好啊 肖恩
Hello, Shawn.
我是你的新死党
I'm your new best friend.
交通监控显示那辆卡车沿着威尔逊街北行
Okay, traffic cameras show the truck heading north on Wilson,
经过了第一个和第二个监控
past first and second,
但没出现在第三个上
but it never got to third.
等等 那是在…
Wait a second. That's … that's by the …
没错
Yeah.
你想要我的什么
You want my what?
别管我想要什么了
Forget what I want.
你想要什么
What do you want?
金钱 美女 荣耀
Money? Women? Glory?
闪闪发光的金腰带
A big, shiny belt?
说出来 就是你的了
Say the word, and it's yours.
因为你是个恶魔吗
Because you're a demon?
生意人罢了
Businessman.
老兄 这到底…
Dude, what the hell is …
看着我 冠军
Eyes on me, champ.
好好想想
Think about it.
再也不用住破烂的小旅馆 去偏僻的小镇
No more crappy motels, podunk towns.
你将过上你一直渴望的生活
You'll have the life you always wanted …
数不尽的女人
gumdrops and g-strings as far as the eye can see.
而我只想要一样东西…
And all I ask in return is …
我的灵魂
My soul.
和你的服务
And your service.
我可能偶尔会让你
See, I might occasionally ask you.
帮我一点点小忙
to do me a teeny, tiny, little favor.
哪种小忙
What kind of favor?
杀人那种
The kill-somebody kind.
为什么选我
Why me?
因为我喜欢你
Because I like you.
你鲁莽 有野心 还很饥渴
You're brash and driven and hungry.
没错
Yeah.
我想找新的经销商
I'm looking for new franchisees.
多一个是一个
Why have one when I can have two?
你答应了
You did this?
加纳就是位心满意足的顾客
Gunnar's what I like to call a satisfied customer.
那么…
So…
成交吗
do we have a deal?
不
No.
听着 老兄
Look, man.
我从不怎么相信上帝什么的
I've never been much for god or whatever.
我一直觉得人大限一到
I sort of just thought that when your curtain came down,
就结束了
that was it.
永别
Night, night.
但假如你是个恶魔 那就意味着有地狱
But if you're a demon, that means there's a hell.
假如有地狱 那就也有天堂
And if there's a hell, there is a heaven.
我不会为了一条我可以自己赢取的腰带
And I'm not giving up my shot at paradise.
而放弃上天堂的机会
for a belt I can win on my own.
是嘛
That so?
你很有天赋 肖恩
You're talented, Shawn.
但人类的躯体 真是太脆弱了
But the human body, it's just so fragile.
一次受伤 走错一步…
One injury, one wrong step…
比如 如果有人…
like, say, if somebody…
割断了你的跟腱
severed your achilles tendon.
你就完了
You're done.
杜克 不要
Duke, no.
该你了
You're up.
他只是个孩子
He's just a kid.
动手
Do it.
这是什么
What is this?
我的私人仓库
My personal lockup …
纪念品 回忆物
keepsakes, mementos,
一些我不希望被那群乌合之众拿到的东西
things I'd prefer the rabble not to get their grubby hands on.
那是你吗
Is that you?
美好的过去啊
Oh, the good old days.
我们来这里干什么
Why are we here?
为了这个
For this.
亚伦之杖
The rod of Aaron …
上帝在第六天创造的
Created by God on the sixth day.
给了亚伦 摩西的哥哥
and given to Aaron, brother of Moses.
我知道它很神奇
I knew it was powerful,
但不知道它还是个
but I had no idea that it was a…
上帝之手
A hand of God.
我可以碰它吗
Can I touch it?
无意冒犯 西蒙斯
With all due respect, Simmons,
我觉得你驾驭不了我的棍子
I don't think you can handle my rod.
我肯定行
I bet I can.
只有我觉得
Is it just me, or…
你刚刚说到了生殖器吗
is it getting a little phallic in here?
放下刀
Drop it.
这真是个惊喜
Isn't this a fun surprise?
你真觉得你可以背叛我
You really thought you could double-cross me?
我
Me?
那个词可是我发明的
You know I invented the double-cross?
真是这样
Like, literally?
当然 如果没有可爱 聪敏的西蒙斯
Of course, I couldn't have orchestrated all of this.
我不可能
without the lovely,
安排好这一切
talented Simmons here.
顺便一提 她恨你
She, um … she hates you, B-T-dubs.
我确实恨你
Yeah. I really do.
他们都恨你
Yeah, they all do.
地狱里每个恶魔都是
Like, every demon in hell.
这怪不得他们 对吧
Can't really blame them, can you?
也许
I mean, maybe.
你曾经是史上最邪恶的
once you were the evilest evil that ever…
邪恶者 包括我在内
eviled … present company excluded.
但现在
But now…
你就只是迪恩·温彻斯特的头号迷弟
You're nothing but Dean winchester's number-one fan.
萨姆和迪恩
Sam and Dean.
我得承认 听过那么多故事
I got to admit … after all the stories,
我还对你们有些
I thought you'd be…
期待呢
more.
让你失望真是抱歉了
Well, sorry to disappoint.
是我的错 不该抱太大期望
It's my fault. You get your hopes up.
想要10分的洛杉矶美人
You want an L.A. 10,
却安于堪萨斯的5分女人
but you settle for a Kansas 5.
人生无常
Life, right?
- 我叫 - 我们不在乎
- The name's… - We don't care.
好吧 闲聊结束
Okay. Small talk over.
杀了他们
Kill them.
加纳 加纳 别 等等
Gunnar, Gunnar, no. Wait.
迪恩
Dean!
我知道你藏了什么
I knew you were hiding something.
我在你眼里看见了最后一丝抵抗的光芒
I could see that last spark of defiance in your eyes.
我没有酷刑逼供
And rather than beating it out of you, which …
虽然可行 但太麻烦
doable, but messy …
我让你领我到这儿来
I let you lead me here.
我要带走这个
So I'm gonna take this…
然后再收拾你
…and then I'm gonna take you.
还有 狗狗
And, oh, puppy,
你不会喜欢接下来要发生的事的
you're not gonna like what comes next.
在找这个吗
You looking for this?
你真觉得你可以背叛我
You really think you could double-cross me?
我
Me?!
我完善了这个词
I perfected the double-cross.
真是这样
Like, literally.
这就是身为上帝的感觉
So, this is what it feels like to be God.
还不赖
Not bad.
挺刺激
Tingly.
如果这东西
So, if this can hurt something.
能伤害黑暗那样强大的存在
as powerful as the Darkness,
对你使用又会怎样呢
I wonder… what can it do to you?
对不起 孩子 我并不想这么做
Sorry, kid. I don't want to do this.
那就住手
Oh, then don't.
我别无选择
You say that like I got a choice.
外面那人 他是个
That guy out there, he's a …
是个恶魔 我知道
He's a demon. I know.
我还知道地狱和交易什么的
And I know about hell and deals … all of it.
他有你什么把柄
What's he got over you?
你卖了自己的灵魂 对吗
You sold your soul, didn't you?
10年前
10 years ago,
我想再争取一次腰带
I wanted another shot at that belt.
五万人 尖叫我的名字
50, 000 people screaming my name.
我当时不顾一切 犯了傻
I was desperate and dumb.
但你只当了一周冠军
But you only had the title for like a week.
所以说不顾一切 犯了傻
Desperate and dumb.
好吧
Okay.
你搞砸了 好吗
Look, you screwed up, all right?
相信我 我也经历过
Trust me. I've been there.
但做对的事 永远为时不晚
But it is never too late to do the right thing.
你真相信吗
You really believe that?
我必须相信
I have to.
你让我流血了
You made me bleed my own blood.
没法力了吧
You're out of juice, huh?
该死
Bollocks.
克劳力知道你这么做吗
Does Crowley know you're doing this?
克劳力是路西法的走狗
Crowley's Lucifer's bitch boy,
所以我才这么做
which is why I'm doing this.
偷灵魂吗
Stealing souls?
存点储备金
Building a nest egg.
黑暗在外 魔鬼掌管地狱
With the Darkness out and the devil running hell,
现在每个恶魔都得为自己打算
well, it's kind of every demon for him/her/shimself.
那你为什么需要劳里斯
So why do you need Lawless?
我不能身处多处
Well, I can't be everywhere.
交易到期时 我便让他选择
When the G-man's deal came due, I gave him a choice …
要么喂地狱之犬 要么为我收集灵魂
end up hellhound chow or collect souls for me.
我委派他了
I'm delegating.
好的管理者就这么做
That's what good managers do.
哎呦 帅哥
Hey, yourself, handsome.
这是我最喜欢的部分
Now, this … this is my favorite part.
谢了
Thanks.
迪恩
Dean.
迪恩 你没事吧
Dean. Hey. You all right?
我很好 我很好
Yeah, I'm good. I'm good.
怎么了
What?
地狱之犬
Hellhounds.
我一直好奇它们叫起来什么样
I always wondered what they'd sound like.
听着 老兄
Listen, man.
你
You, uh…
不
No.
我一直不是个好人
I've never been a good man.
我看着镜子
I look in the mirror.
我憎恨镜子里看着我的人
and I hate the face looking back at me.
不 我
No, I, uh…
我是自找的
I got this coming.
走吧
Go on.
出去
Get out.
快走
Now.
你还好吧
Are you okay?
一点都不好
Not even a little bit.
劳里斯是个好人
Lawless was a good guy.
他不该那样惨死 你知道吗
He didn't deserve to go out like that, you know?
迪恩 他做了错误的决定
Dean, you know what? He made a bad decision.
我们都经历过
We've been there.
对
Yeah.
对 你 我 现在是小卡
Yeah, you, me, now Cass.
迪恩 我们会救回他
Dean, we'll get him back.
我们会的 我们只要
We will. We just got to …
继续撑着
Keep grinding.
不管有多痛 不管有多难
No matter how much it hurts, no matter how hard it gets,
要继续撑着
You got to keep grinding.
对
Right.
我们就要这样赢
And that's how we're gonna win.
我们会赢的
And we're gonna win.
我们会救回小卡 我们会杀了魔鬼
We're gonna save Cass, we're gonna ice the devil,
我们会干掉黑暗
and we're gonna shank the Darkness.
谁挡路
And anyone that gets in our way,
谁就别想活
well, god help them.
没错
Damn right.